Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- N, 1899-2012; 18.5 Linear Feet in 16 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize shared boxes, and 1 shared manuscript box
  - National Citizens' Committee for Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday, 1971 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens' Committee for Justice for J. P. Stevens Workers, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - National Citizens' Committee for the Protection of Civil Rights in the Automobile Industry, 1937 (Box 61)
  - National Citizens Committee to Defend Academic Freedom at St. Johns University (New York), undated (Box 61)
  - National Citizens' New Year's Eve Peace Observance, undated (Box 61)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee, 1944-1946, undated (Box 61)
  - National Civic Federation, 1913-1934 (Box 61)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau I, 1917- (Box 61)
  - National Civil Liberties Bureau II, 1917- (Box 62)
  - National Civil Rights Legislative Conference, 1949 (Box 62)
  - National Civil Service Reform League, 1912 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship, 2003-2011 (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 3)
  - National Coalition Against War, Racism, and Repression, 1970-1973 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1987- (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Fight Inflation and Unemployment, 1975 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Sign the Treaty Now!, 1973 (Box 62)
  - National Coalition to Stop the Rock, undated (Box 62)
  - National Colombia Mobilization, 2003 (Box 62)
  - National Commission for the Defense of Democracy through Education (Washington, DC), undated (Box 62)
  - National Commission on Working Women, 1978-1984 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Censorship of the Theater Arts, 1935 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1951-1971, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1973, 1989 (Box 62)
  - National Committee Against the Treaty of Moscow, 1960s (Box 62)
  - National Committee: Continental Congress, circa 1933 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Fair Minimum Wage, 1945 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Free Europe: Pamphlets, 1948-1951 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Political Settlement in Vietnam, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1968, undated (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 4)
  - National Committee for Defense of Political Prisoners, 1936 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Full Employment, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Independent Political Action (NCIPA), 1987-1992 (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 5)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel, 1956-1957 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Peoples Rights, 1941 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Repeal of the McCarran Act, 1964-1965 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools, 1960 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for Student Mobilization for Peace, 1935 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Albany Defendants (Georgia), 1964 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Civil Rights in Tampa, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Joanne Chesimard and Clark Souire, 1973-1974 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners, 1937, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners, 1974-1975 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education, 1948-1950 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the New Party (Ottawa, Canada), 1961 (Box 62)
  - National Committee for the Student Congress Against War (New York, NY), undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee of Unemployed Councils, 1930s (Box 62)
  - National Committee of Yugoslavia for the Defense of Peace, 1950 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Atomic Information, 1947 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Employment of Youth, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Labor Injunctions, 1938 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on Prisons and Prison Labor, 1922 (Box 62)
  - National Committee on the Churches and World Peace, 1930 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee I, 1961-1969 (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 10)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee II, 1961-1969 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee III, 1961-1969 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax, 1943-1945 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defeat the Mundt Bill (Washington, DC), undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend and Support Johnny Coward and Bartee Haile, circa 1970 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend Negro Leadership, 1954 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend New Afrikan Freedom Fighters, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Defend the Bakke Decision, circa 1977 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Free the Five (Cuba), undated (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 6)
  - National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case, 1976-1998 (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 7)
  - National Committee to Repeal the McCarran Act, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Secure Justice in the Rosenberg-Sobell Case, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Uphold Constitutional Government, undated (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Win Amnesty for Smith Act Victims (New York, NY), 1954-1955 (Box 62)
  - National Committee to Win the Peace (Washington, DC), 1946 (Box 62)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1967-1968, undated (Box 62, Box 127, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of American Socialists, 1958 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Charities and Collections, Proceedings (Boston, MA), Jun 1911 (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews (New York, NY), 1943-1954, undated (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Labor, Socialist and Radical Movements (New York, NY), 1918 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Fundamental Problems in the Education of Negroes (Washington, DC), 1934 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Lynching (New York, NY), 1919 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Organized Resistance, 2001- (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Public Service Employment (New York, NY), 1971-1973 (Box 62)
  - National Conference on Soviet Jewry, undated (Box 62)
  - National Conference of Synagogue Youth, undated (Box 62)
  - National Congress for Puerto Rican Rights, 1987 (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Employees (Piermont, NY), 1985-1986 (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Neighborhood Women (New York, NY), circa 1970s (Box 63)
  - National Congress of Unemployed Organizations (Chicago, IL), circa 1984 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1911-1928 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1929-1934 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, 1935-1965 (Box 63)
  - National Consumers' League, undated (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Center in Solidarity with Chile, 1975-1976 (Box 63)
  - National Co-operative Men's Guild (Great Britain), 1924 (Box 63)
  - National Co-operative Society, undated (Box 63)
  - National Cooperatives, Inc. I, 1939-1947 (Box 63)
  - National Cooperatives, Inc. II, 1939-1947 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Center in Solidarity with Chile, 1976 (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1971- (Box 63)
  - National Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 63)
  - National Council Against Conscription (Washington, DC), 1947-1954, undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for American Education (New York, NY), 1952 (Box 63)
  - National Council for a Permanent Fair Employment Practice Committee (Washington, DC), 1944-1947 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Civil Liberties (Great Britain), 1922-1984 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Democratic Aid (Great Britain), undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Democratic Rights (Toronto, Canada), undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Industrial Peace (Washington, DC), 1960, undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Peace and Against Nuclear Weapons (Japan), undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Prevention of War, 1923-1941, undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Protection of Foreign Born Workers (New York, NY), undated (Box 63)
  - National Council for Social Democracy, 1939 (Box 63)
  - National Council for Universal and Unconditional Amnesty (New York, NY), 1976 (Box 63)
    Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection of Oversized Material (PE 040) also contains a National Council for Universal and Unconditional Amnesty file.
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship I, 1943-1947 (Box 63, Box 127, Folder 9)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship II, 1943- (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship III, 1943- (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Committee of Women, 1949 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets I, 1940-1949 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, 1940-1949 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets III, 1940-1949 (Box 63)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets IV, 1940-1949 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets I, 1950-1959 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, 1950-1959 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets III, 1950-1959 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets, 1960-1969 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, 1960-1969 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets, 1970-1975 (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets I, undated (Box 64)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: Pamphlets II, undated (Box 64)
  - National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1947, undated (Box 64)
  - National Council of Jewish Communists (New York, NY), 1939 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, 1956 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Labor (Great Britain), 1936-1938 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Labour Colleges (Great Britain) I, 1935-1958 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Labour Colleges (Great Britain) II, 1935-1958 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Methodist Youth, 1938 (Box 64)
  - National Council of Scientific, Professional, Art and White Collar Organizations, 1944 (Box 64)
  - National Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, 1948-1954 (Box 64)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA, 1963-1965 (Box 64)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA: Pamphlets I, 1952-1967 (Box 64)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA: Pamphlets II, 1952-1967 (Box 64)
  - National Council on Freedom from Censorship (New York, NY), 1939, undated (Box 64)
  - National Council of Household Employment, undated (Box 64)
  - National Council to Repeal the Draft (Washington, DC), 1967-1973 (Box 64, Box 127, Folder 11)
  - National Defense Organization Against Racist and Political Repression, circa 1973 (Box 64)
  - National Democratic Party of Alabama (NDPA), undated (Box 64)
  - National Democratic Policy Committee I, 1980-1983 (Box 64)
    This file contains information about Lyndon LaRouche.
  - National Democratic Policy Committee II, 1980-1983 (Box 64)
  - National Democratic Policy Committee III, 1980-1983 (Box 64)
  - National Democratic Policy Committee IV, 1980-1983 (Box 65)
  - National Economic Boycott, undated (Box 65)
  - National Educational Committee for a New Party, 1946, undated (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (New York, NY) I, 1953-1980 (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (New York, NY) II, 1953-1980 (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (New York, NY) III, 1953-1980 (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Civil Rights Mobilization (New York, NY), 1949 (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Committee on Lebanon (New York, NY), undated (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Committee on the Middle East (New York, NY), 1983 (Box 65)
  - National Emergency Conference (Cleveland, Ohio), undated (Box 65)
  - National Farm Organization, 1963 (Box 65)
  - National Farmworkers Association, undated (Box 65)
  - National Fatherland Front of the Democratic Republic of Afghanistan, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties, 1940 (Box 65)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties I, 1941-1945 (Box 65)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties II, 1941-1945 (Box 65)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties: Academic Council, 1944 (Box 65)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties: Pamphlets, 1940-1942 (Box 65)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties: Pamphlets, 1944-1946, undated (Box 65)
  - National Federation of American Shipping, Inc. (Washington, DC), 1947- (Box 65)
  - National Fight Back Organization, 1977, undated (Box 65, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 20)
  - National Finnish Organization of United States of America (Socialist Party), 1914 (Box 65)
  - National Foremen's Institute, 1942-1957 (Box 65)
  - National Forum (Chicago, IL), 1938 (Box 65)
  - National Forward-to-the-Land League, undated (Box 65)
  - National Front of Democratic Germany, 1966 (Box 65)
  - National Garment Label Council (New York, NY), undated (Box 65)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (New York, NY), 1973- (Box 65)
  - National Gay Liberation Task Force, 1971 (Box 65)
  - National Grass Rooters Interested in Poverty Elimination (New York, NY), 1969 (Box 65)
  - National Grays Harbor Committee, circa 1940 (Box 65)
  - National Guardian (New York, NY), 1965-1967, undated (Box 65)
  - National Hard Times Conference (Chicago, IL), 1976 (Box 65)
  - National Immigrant Solidarity Network, 2004, undated (Box 65)
  - National Indian Youth Council, Inc. (Albuquerque, NM), 1975-1981 (Box 65)
  - National Independent Politics Summit, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - National Industrial Conference Board I, 1924-1961 (Box 65)
  - National Industrial Conference Board II, 1924-1961 (Box 65)
  - National Institute of Labor Education (Madison, WI) I, 1957-1967 (Box 65)
  - National Institute of Labor Education (Madison, WI) II, 1957-1967 (Box 65)
  - National Institute of Labor Education (Madison, WI) III, 1957-1967 (Box 65)
  - National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People (New York, NY) I, 1973-1974, undated (Box 65)
  - National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People (New York, NY) II, 1973-1974, undated (Box 66)
  - National Interreligious Service Board for Conscientious Objectors (Washington, DC), circa 1980 (Box 66)
  - National Jewish Organization, 1969 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Alliance for Trade Relations with and Recognition of Russia (New York, NY), undated (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee (New York, NY) I, 1998- (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee (New York, NY) II, 1998- (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee (New York, NY) III, 1998- (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights (New York, NY), 2002- (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee for the Jewish Workers in Palestine (New York, NY), undated (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee for Wallace and Taylor (New York, NY), circa 1948 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador (New York, NY), 1983-1991 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights (New York, NY), 1998- (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee of the Progressive Party, undated (Box 66)
  - National Labor Committee to Defend Al Lannon (New York, NY), undated (Box 66)
    Al Lannon was prosecuted under the Smith Act.
  - National Labor Committee to Elect McGovern-Shriver (Washington, DC), 1972 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Conference for Safe Energy and Full Employment (Pittsburgh, PA), 1980 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Congress: Clippings, 1868 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Law Center, 1982, undated (Box 66)
  - National Labor Relations Board (Washington, DC), 1959, undated (Box 66)
  - National Labor Service I, 1947-1959 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Service II, 1947-1959 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Service I, 1960-1974 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Service II, 1960-1974 (Box 66)
  - National Labor Service, undated (Box 66)
  - National Labour Press (London, U.K.), 1948, undated (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild I, 1937-2000 (Box 66, Box 127, Folder 14)
  - National Lawyers Guild II, 1937-1986, undated (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Annual Dinner, 1944, 1976 (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Brochures, 1959-1965, undated (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Convention I, 1937-1967 (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Convention II, 1937-1967 (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Detroit Chapter, 1943, 1977 (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: New York Chapter I, 1945-1983, undated (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: New York Chapter II, 1945-1983, undated (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: Pamphlets and Publications, 1943- (Box 66)
  - National Lawyers Guild: San Francisco Chapter, 1984, undated (Box 66)
  - National League for the Release of Political Prisoners (Chicago, IL), 1919 (Box 66)
  - National League of Women Voters, 1923-1946 (Box 66)
  - National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, 1965 (Box 66)
  - National Libertarian League, 1969 (Box 66)
  - National Livelihood Association (Winter Park, FL), undated (Box 67)
  - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1919 (Box Shared Tamiment 189, Folder 21)
  - National Minority Movement (London, U.K.) II, 1924-1928, undated (Box 67)
  - National Minority Movement (London, U.K.) I, 1924-1928, undated (Box 67)
  - National Mobilization Against Racism, 1986 (Box 67)
  - National Mobilization Against Sweatshops (NMASS) (New York, NY), 1998- (Box 67)
  - National Mobilization Committee, undated (Box 67)
  - National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1967-1970, undated (Box 67, Box 127, Folder 15)
  - National Museum of Labour History (Great Britain), 1986- (Box 67)
  - National Negro Congress, 1936-1941, 1946 (Box 67)
  - National Negro Congress: Pamphlets, 1940-1946, undated (Box 67)
  - National Negro Labor Council (Detroit, MI), 1952-1953 (Box 67)
  - National Network for Immigrant and Refugee Rights (Oakland, CA), 1989 (Box 67)
  - National Network of Marxist-Leninist Clubs, 1979, undated (Box 67)
  - National Network on Cuba, undated (Box 67)
  - National Non-Partisan Committee (New York, NY), undated (Box 67)
  - National Non-Partisan League (St. Paul, MN) I, 1917, undated (Box 67)
  - National Non-Partisan League (St. Paul, MN) II, 1917, undated (Box 67)
  - National Organization for an American Revolution, 1972-1978 (Box 67)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) I, 1966, undated (Box 67, Box 127, Folder 16)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) II, 1966- (Box 67)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) III, 1966- (Box 67)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) IV, 1966- (Box 67)
  - National Organization for Women: New York City Chapter, 1981- (Box 67)
  - National Organizers Alliance, undated (Box 67)
  - National Organizing Committee to Found a Communist Youth Organization, undated (Box 67)
  - National Party (Chicago, IL), 1917-1918 (Box 67)
  - National Peace Academy Campaign (Washington, DC), circa 1980s (Box 67)
  - National Peace Action Coalition (New York, NY) I, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - National Peace Action Coalition (New York, NY) II, 1971-1972 (Box 67)
  - National Peace Conference (New York, NY), 1936-1945 (Box 68)
  - National Peace Council (Great Britain), 1940-1945, undated (Box 68)
  - National People's Campaign (New York, NY), 1997 (Box 68)
  - National Planning Association I, 1942-1964 (Box 68)
  - National Planning Association II, 1942-1967 (Box 68)
  - National Planning Association: Pamphlets I, 1941-1963 (Box 68)
  - National Planning Association: Pamphlets II, 1941-1963 (Box 68)
  - National Policy Committee, 1945 (Box 68)
  - National Popular Government League (Washington, DC), 1918-1940 (Box 68)
  - National Prisoners' Reform Association (Cranston, RI), 1976 (Box 68)
  - National Probation Association (New York, NY), 1930 (Box 68)
  - National Progressive Women Suffrage Union, undated (Box 68)
  - National Progressive Congress, 1932 (Box 68)
  - National Prohibition Party, circa 1912 (Box 68)
  - National Publicity Council for Health and Welfare Services (New York, NY), 1954 (Box 68)
  - National Rank and File Conference: Chicago, 1970 (Box 68)
  - National Rank and File Conference: Arrangements Committee, 1970 (Box 68)
  - National Rank and File Movement (Great Britain), undated (Box 68)
  - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1943-1955 (Box 68)
  - National Renaissance Party (New York, NY), undated (Box 68)
  - National Resource Center on Political Prisoners in the Philippines (Oakland, CA), 1977 (Box 68)
  - National Right to Work Committee, 1981, undated (Box 68)
  - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation I, 1973 (Box 68)
  - National Right to Work Legal Defense Foundation II, 1973- (Box 68)
  - National Right to Work Congress, undated (Box 68)
  - National Sanctuary Defense Fund (San Francisco, CA), 1986 (Box 68)
  - National Secular Society (London, U.K.), 1921 (Box 68)
  - National Security League (New York, NY), 1918-1920 (Box 68)
  - National Service Board for Religious Objectors, 1942-1966 (Box 68)
  - National Sharecroppers' Fund I, 1944-1967 (Box 68)
  - National Sharecroppers' Fund II, 1944-1964 (Box 68)
  - National Sharecroppers' Fund: Rurual Advancement Fund, 1969-1973 (Box 68)
  - National Social Unit Organization, 1917-1918, undated (Box 68)
  - National Socialist (Washington, DC): Election Campaign Handbook, 1913 (Box 68)
  - National Socialist White People's Party, circa 1968 (Box 68)
  - National States Rights Party: New Jersey Chapter, undated (Box 68)
  - National Strike for Peace, 1970 (Box 68)
  - National Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975 (Box 68)
  - National Student Committee for Civil Liberties, undated (Box 68)
  - National Student Coordinating Committee, 1972 (Box 68)
  - National Student Council for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1958-1961, undated (Box 68)
  - National Student Federation of America, 1927-1928 (Box 68)
  - National Student Forum, 1924 (Box 68)
  - National Student League, 1935, undated (Box 68)
  - National Tenants Organization (Washington, DC), 1970 (Box 68)
  - National Trade Union Committee for Racial Justice (New York, NY), circa 1955 (Box 68)
  - National Trade Union Council for Human Rights, 1966-1980 (Box 68)
  - National Unemployed and Welfare Rights Organizations, 1973-1974, undated (Box 68)
  - National Unemployment Council, 1935-1936 (Box 68)
  - National Unemployment League, 1924-1930 (Box 68)
  - National Union for Social Justice, 1935 (Box 68)
  - National Union of Democratic Teachers, 1976 (Box 69)
  - National Union of Students (Great Britain), 1948- (Box 69)
  - National United Front of Kampuchea, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - National United Workers Organization, 1977, undated (Box 69)
  - National Unity Campaign Committee (Great Britain): Pamphlet, 1937 (Box 69)
  - National Urban League I, 1932- (Box 69)
  - National Urban League II, 1932- (Box 69)
  - National Venceremos Brigade, 1973-1992 (Box 69, Box 127, Folder 18)
  - National [George] Wallace Campaign, 1972 (Box 69)
  - National [Henry] Wallace for President Committee I, 1948 (Box 69)
  - National [Henry] Wallace for President Committee II, 1948 (Box 69)
  - National [Henry] Wallace for President Committee III, 1948 (Box 69)
  - National War Savings Committee (London, U.K.), 1918 (Box 69)